[{"answer": "Well, look, well, from the U.S. point of view, their contention that the White House is, they have the information in hand that could lead the President to make that decision.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "What's the very latest you're hearing about a U.S. Military strike?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, certainly not I wouldn't think days.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Do we have any indication?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Do you think this would be a mistake for the U.S. to act militarily, why?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I hear allegations similar to that and I say I don't exclude that have taken place.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "But let me get back to the suggestion that -- I think you were suggesting that maybe the opposition, the rebels, have been using chemical weapons, is there any evidence you've seen that they have?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "I'm not sure that the American people want to be the world police.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "So when they present this evidence publicly today to the American people, to the international community, as far as you're concerned that's not good enough?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do you think it's possible he's right again this time?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "No, we did not.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "For you, did you hear the actual voice of Syrian commanders speaking about ordering chemical weapons to be used?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think to compare what's going now with Iraq is like comparing apples with oranges.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Was that good enough for you then?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I think the real question is what are we trying to achieve with whatever strikes the President may authorize.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "What would Iran do?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "No, I think he has to do something because he basically said publicly some time ago, before the first attacks, chemical attacks earlier this year.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Well, after the President of the United States draws that red line, after we heard very strong comments from the Secretary of state Today and later from the President today, if the U.S. were to do nothing militarily, what kind of message would that send?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, I think there should be a -- I'm not an expert on what the target set might be.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Much more -- instead of just a few tomahawk cruise missiles, what else would you want him to do?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "It doesn't sound like it.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Do you think it's possible U.S. intelligence is now flawed again?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Wolf, all the targets have already been identified, the software has been uploaded so that the very latest targeting information has -- is available.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "If the President signs the order, General Marks, how quickly for that order be implemented to target the various locations in Syria?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Well, I mean they have to have the publicity to go forward with this.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "In other words all this publicity?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Is the President of United States who himself once taught law at the University of Chicago, a graduate of the Harvard Law School, is he potentially going to violate international law if you believe Jimmy Carter?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Wolf, if I would suggest, he should be a 100 percent convinced that the United States will be dragged into something that they choose not to be.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Spider, the -- I know the President's intention is not to go in for anything more than a limited, very precise operation, but can he be 100 percent sure the U.S. won't be dragged into something much more substantial depending on the Syrian response?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "You know, Wolf, because it seems clear to me that we are on the eve of decision to engage in military operations.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What kind of marks, Fran, will you give the current national security team surrounding the President on this sensitive subject?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, if that were the case, then every lawful act that has been taken by every president since 1941 will be unlawful.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, what do you think?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "If you knew then what you know now, would you have played football, Jim?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I don't think in all cases they were, no.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Do you believe, knowing what you know now that the NFL team doctors were looking out for the best interest of the players?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "No, I've been wearing sun glasses since I was 6 years old.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Is that why you're wearing the glasses right now, the sun glasses?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "I think it's a great result for a great group of people.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "The amount of money the players are going to receive?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "No, there really isn't.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Larry how money you think Jim is going to receive as part of the settlement?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I think they're finally realizing what, you know, what this -- the damage that can be done to the brain.", "docId": "130830pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Is this sport safe?", "qSentId": 429}]